This is a work of fiction. Names, characters,
places and incidents either are products of the
author’s imagination or are used fictitiously. Any
resemblance to actual events or locales or
persons, living or dead, is entirely coincidental.
うわっ 高っ
3万か… こっちは20万
Whoa, that's pricey!
自分でパーツ集めればもっと安上がりになるけど
Thirty thousand?
And that one's 200 thousand.
そんな時間ないし
It'd just be cheaper to buy the parts and build it ourselves,
お小遣い前借りは１万円まで
but we don't have time for that now.
そっか じゃあ 手は１つしかないね
I can only get ten thousand of my allowance in advance too...
何?
I see. Then we only have one choice.
ROBO-ONE出場を諦める
That is?
んにゃろ
Give up on entering the Robo-One.
飯時はよせって
何でそうすぐ諦める方に持ってくわけ
Geez!
もっとあがこうよ
Let me eat in peace!
あがいたところで 無理でしょ
Why do you have to suggest giving up right away?!
ホビーロボットもないのに 2週間後の大会で優勝なんて
At least struggle a little!
How would struggling change anything?
そうだ
We don't even have a hobby robot,
何
あるよ ホビーロボット
so how do you plan on winning a
tournament two weeks from now?
どこに
Oh right!
部室に
What?
輝かしいロボット部の名誉部長
We do have a hobby robot!
Where's that?
In the club room!
タネガシマシン3が
Our glorious club president from the shiny days,
本字幕由诸神字幕组出品，仅供学习交流之用 更多中日双语字幕，请登录 www.kamigami.org
--诸神字幕组---
台本：卷
翻译:mam
校对: maize
后期:Ressul zzz
Tanegashimachine-3!
すれ違う　言葉の裏に
閉ざされた　心の鍵
Behind the words passing by
The key of my closed heart is hidden
君という　フラグ開錠が
笑顔救えるのなら
If setting your flag
Could save your smile
夏の風誘う　迫真のスコール
The late summer breeze
波長シンクロ
Turns into a midday squall
ロマンチックみたいに　気の利いた言葉も
As we sync our wavelengths
I'm such a bad romantic
見つからないけど　青空を目指すから
Can't even find
Any words with an edge
Still I aim for the blue sky
僕たちは　一つになれる
戸惑いの涙も　夢も
We can become one
As our dreams and confused tears
真実に　引き寄せられるなら
Draw us ever closer to the truth
それは愛しすぎる
魔法の日を
That becomes our beloved
Magical keyword
Because we're romantics with hopes and dreams
動け 動け
Move! Move!
もう8年も前のでしょ
This thing is 8 years old.
Do you seriously expect it to move?
動くわけないよ
Gunvarrel could move because of Genki!
ゲンキ君の勇気がガンヴァレルに力を与えたでしょ
動け 動くんだ ガンヴァレル
Move! Move for me, Gunvarrel!
やっぱりバッテリーがいっちゃってるのかなぁ
It must be the battery...
充電器もないし
We don't have a charger either.
Are we buying one?
新しく買う?
I bet it'd be expensive...
でも高いだろうし
そんなに分解しちゃって 大丈夫なの
Is it okay to take it apart like that?
It's okay. I'm just taking the screws out.
大丈夫 ねじ外してるだけだし
Could you look for a servo test board in the storeroom next door?
それより 隣の倉庫行ってサーボ用テストボード捜してみてくれない
Fine. If you can beat me at Kill Bal—
分かった
じゃあ 『キルバラ』で勝負を…
I won't.
しないから
そのくらい いいでしょ
You can't even do that much?
そのくらいかどうか アキちゃんが行ってみるといいよ
See for yourself how much it is.
ケチ
Meanie.
分かった
Okay, I'll look for a test board myself.
テストボードはうちが捜すから
カイ オペレーターやってくんない
Could you be the operator?
Operator?
オペレーター?
タネガシマシン3の操縦者だよ
You'd control Tanegashimachine-3.
You play Kill Ballad all the time anyway,
いつも 『キルバラ』やってるし
so I think you'll be good at it.
うちより得意だと思うんだよね
だったら 『キルバラ』のがいいな
Then I'll just play Kill Ballad.
How about I put a cannon on Tanegashimachine-3.
じゃあ タネガシマシン3にキャノン付けてあげる
それなら いいでしょ
キャノンって 何撃つの
A cannon? What would it shoot?
It'd just be a big decoration,
もちろん 飾り
でも外見は やる気に大きく関わってくるでしょ
but appearances have a huge effect on people's will to fight.
I'd love it if it had a finishing move and a transformation scene too...
あと 必殺技と変形合体も欲しいところなんだけど
Aki...
アキちゃん
What?
何
What are you going for?
優先させるのは見た目? 結果?
Looks or results?
Results.
結果
Oh really?
そう?
Quit it already. I got it!
もう 分かったよ
Anyway,
とは言ったものの
even if everything else worked,
他のところはともかく 電源は大本だからね
we can't do anything without a battery.
We can't substitute it for something else either.
何かで代用ってわけにもいかないし
What are you gonna do?
どうするつもり?
Of course...
もちろん…
I'll barter!
交渉あるのみ
Hey, Doc!
こんにちは ドク
音 下げて
Turn the volume down!
Turn it down!
音 下げてよ
Or have you gone deaf with age alre—
それでなくても 年で耳が遠い…
Ah.
Hello, Doc.
こんちは ドク
I've given you parts already.
パーツなら この前くれてやったろうが
I don't have anything to spare.
もう 分けてやるもんはねえぞ
And you, guy! Don't you know how to say hello?
それと付き添い
挨拶もねえのか
Long time no see...
ご無沙汰です
Doc, actually it's not about the GunPro-1 this time.
ドク 実は今日はガンつく1の件じゃないの
It's this...
これなんだけど
Oh? Robo-One, huh?
ROBO-ONEか
こんな古いもん 今手に入るわけねえだろ
Do you seriously expect me to have something this old?
Well, I hoped...
やっぱり?
メーカー替えるしかねえな
You'll have to use a different maker.
Something compatible with the Ogawada S plug.
オガワダのSプラグ対応でどうだ
What do you say?
Um... How much?
えっと お値段は?
8000 and a beer.
8,000ちょいか
Too expensive!
ツー エクスペンシィィブ
I'm already discounting the shipping for you, damn club kiddo.
これでも 送料まけてやってんだ
このくそロボ部が
くそとか言わないでよ
Don't say "damn"....
Oh well. Do you have something else then?
仕方ねえな
じゃあ 他に何かねえのか
他のパーツまとめて買うんなら 考えてやる
I might give it a thought if you buy something else too.
Really?!
本当ですか
Then a 360° camera?
じゃあ 360度の全方位カメラを
Are you nuts? That won't even do as decoration.
バカか カメラなんて飾りにもなんねえぞ
はっきり言う 気に入らんな
I'll be blunt: I don't like this.
何だ そりゃ
What are you talking about?
Well, for the Robo-One a gyro would be the best.
ROBO-ONEならジャイロだろうな
Together with that battery you can get it for twelve thousand.
さっきのと合わせて 1万2,000にしといてやる
Could you make that ten?
合わせて1万ぽっきりで
Non-negotiable.
交渉決裂だな
I don't have that much money!
お金がないんです
You're doing business with high school kids!
相手は高校生じゃないですか
Make it a student discount! A student discount plan!
学割 学割プランで
Not a chance!
知るか
うちはプロとしてやってんだ
I'm working for my living here! Take it or leave it!
嫌なら出ていけ
Oh geez!
イーッだ
What do we do now?
でもどうするの
He won't give you the stuff unless you pay up.
ドク お金を持ってこないかぎり品物は渡さないって言ってたよ
Can you ask for your allowance ahead of time?
カイの家って お小遣い前借りできる?
『キルバラ』勝負 やろっか
How about a Kill Ballad game?
ホント カイってめんどくさい
You're a real pain in the neck.
You're preparing for the Robo-One? People are talking about it in school.
RORO-ONEの準備ですか
校内で話題になってますよ
Saying it's a reckless challenge.
無謀な挑戦だってね
So what?
だから何
If we win, we can get the club budget we need!
優勝すれば どどーんと部費が手に入るんだから
But you won't win.
無理ですよ
ROBO-ONEはそんなに甘い大会じゃない
The Robo-One isn't such an easy tournament.
Even suggesting total amateurs could win it after two weeks is offensive.
三流素人が2週間で行くなんて 失礼です
Miracles are there for us to make them happen!
でも 奇跡は起こすためにある
"Ever since Hidaka Subaru, who won third place in the Robo-One during junior high, agreed to help—"
中学時代 ROBO-ONE3位の実績を持つ日高昴が
協力を申し出たときから…
I refuse.
お断りします
Blunt as always...
相変わらずばっさり
What about you, Yashio?
八汐先輩はいいんですか
You're wasting your time tagging along with her.
付き合っても時間の無駄ですよ
I guess so...
そうだなぁ
でも あの部室『キルバラ』やるにはちょうどいい環境だから
But the club room's a perfect place to play Kill Ballad.
Is that your reason?!
えーっ それが理由?
I see.
そうですか
さすが変わり者って評判の八汐先輩だけはありますね
You sure live up to your weirdo image.
じゃあ
See you.
あれ でも日高君はどうしてここに来たの
But why are you here?
別に 通り掛かっただけですよ
I just happened by.
Anyway, go ahead and have your fun.
まあ せいぜい楽しんでくださいよ
It's the last activity of the Robot Club, after all.
ロボ部最後の活動を
Geez! You stupid kid!
この 坊やだからさ
He's right, you know.
でも 日高君が言ってることは正しいよ
There's no way we can win.
どう考えても優勝するのは無理だと思う
But then what about the GunPro-1?
そんな ガンつく1はどうなるの
個人で造り続けることもできるでしょ
You could keep working on it by yourself.
確かにそうだよね
That's true...
でもね うちはロボ部として何とかしたい
But you know,
I want to do it as the Robot Club.
だって お姉ちゃんがつくったロボ部と
It's the Robot Club my sister made
and the GunPro-1 my sister tried to make.
お姉ちゃんが造ろうとしたガンつく1だもん
It's pointless if we don't build it in the club!
ロボ部で造らなきゃ意味ない
Not to mention we do this because we're romantics with hopes and dreams!
それに ロボットは
夢と希望とロマンがあってこそでしょ
Now who's the pain in the neck...
まったく どっちがめんどくさいんだか
アキのこと よろしくね
Take good care of Akiho please.
Irei Store
Welcome!
いらっしゃい
またお前か
It's you again?
Give me that.
あれを1つ下さい
Right away.
はいよ
一気に行きな
Do it at once.
I will!
いただきます
Here it comes! This half-sweet half-sour taste from behind the lukewarm dough...
きた
この生暖かい生地の向こうから
口いっぱいに広がる中途半端な甘味と酸味
Passionfruit tastes so great, so why would you turn it into a Chinese dumpling?!
パッションフルーツは あんなにおいしいのに
なぜ中華まんにした
This is the devil's work! It's straight from hell!
まさに 悪魔の発明
地獄より来たりし者
はい
I'm done.
You pass. The Lake Treaty is now in effect.
合格
ミズウミ協定 成立だよ
But could you try to pretend it's good?
しっかし もう少しうまく食えないもんか
Not a chance. It's challenging enough to just eat.
無理です あれが精いっぱい
Whatever. A promise is a promise.
まあいいや 約束だからね
欲しい情報 1つ言いな
What do you want to know?
聞きたいのは ドクのこと
I want to know about the Doc.
ドク? あの偏屈じじいか
Doc? That old weirdo?
I want to know his weak spot.
弱みとか知りたいんだよね
聞いたら 思わず値下げしちゃいたくなるような
Something that could make him give us a discount.
You want to blackmail him into giving you something?
あのじいさん脅して 商品値切ろうってか
How cunning.
こりゃ傑作だ
Sure, I'll look into it.
分かった
いいよ 調べとく
頼むね
Thanks.
じゃあ
See you.
Whenever you ask for something, Aki's involved.
相変わらず 何か頼むときは全部アキ絡みだな
What are you to her?
お前さ アキの何なんだ
Dunno... Maybe her replacement.
さあ もしかしたら代わりのつもりなのかも ミサ姉の
Misa's, that is.
You're nice...
けなげだね
Both to Aki and to Misa.
アキに対しても ミサに対しても
Anemone
Daitoku?
大徳さん?
From the next class.
隣のクラスの…
You know, that quiet girl from the karate club.
ほら 空手部でおとなしそうな
But wasn't Doc's name Fujita?
でも ドクの名字って藤田じゃなかったっけ
The name might be different, but she's Doc's granddaughter.
名字は違うんだけど 孫らしいんだ ドクの
His granddaughter, huh?
孫か
Then we could ask her!
じゃあ 大徳さんに頼んでもらえれば
There's no need to rush...
何も立ったまま食べなくても
Okay!
よし 1組って言ってたよね
It was class 1, right?
Thank you for the intel.
情報 ありがとうございます
Irei Store
Call duration
End call
また 何かあったら来なよ
Come again if you need something.
I still have plenty of passionfruits left.
パッションフルーツまん たくさん用意して待ってるから
Also...
それと…
I know. I won't tell Aki.
分かってる アキには言わないよ
3rd Year Class 1
すいません 面倒で
Sorry for the trouble.
大徳さん
Daitoku!
My grampa?
おじいちゃんに?
Sorry for asking this of you...
ホント こんなこと頼んで申し訳ないんだけど
But if we can't get the parts from Doc, the club will be disbanded...
ドクにパーツ代払えないと 部が本当になくなっちゃうの
Please!
お願い
ごめん 無理かも…
Sorry, but I don't think I can...
I... Um...
私 その…
I haven't met with Grampa Fujita for years,
何年も藤田のおじいちゃんとは会ってないし
だから…
so...
But...
いや でも
Sorry, I just hoped you could get us a discount.
ごめんね
いや ちょっと安くなるといいなぁって思っただけだから
I'm sorry.
ごめんなさい
そうだ 実は今ロボットの必殺技を開発中なんだけど
Anyway, I'm working on our robot's finishing move now!
Do you have any karate ideas?
空手で何かない
Huh?
相手を倒せる技とか
Something to knock the opponent out.
そう 大徳さんの得意な技とか
Like, your specialty or something.
得意な技?
My specialty?
Yeah.
ない…かも
I don't really have one...
Huh? Really?
そ…そうなんだ
Then how about a kata? You can do those, right?
じゃあ 空手の形
それなら あるでしょ
形だと スーパーリンペイかな
Well, I use the suparinpei...
Eh, that sounds cool!
びびっとくる名前
How do you do it? Hm?
どうやんの どうやんの
But it's not how you imagine it to be...
でも 全然瀬乃宮さんが想像しているようなのじゃなくて
If you want to take your opponent down, then a forward kick...
倒すだけなら 前蹴りとか
A forward kick?
前蹴り?
どうやんの
How do you do that?
Um...
Like this, then this.
こうして こう
Let's see, you raise your leg, then this and thi—
脚を上げて
こうして… こう
大丈夫?
Are you okay?
Ouch...
痛た…
This works well!
これだよ これならロボにもできる
The robot could do it, like this!
ほら見て こう こう
Uh Senomiya, you're lifting your skirt...
いや あの…
瀬乃宮さん パンツ見えちゃうよ
Here, the battery and the charger.
ほらよ バッテリーと充電器
It's so bright and shiny!
きらきらしてる
It still took you a week to pick it up even though I had the shipping rushed.
せっかく急いで取り寄せてやったってのに
1週間も音沙汰なしとはな
I didn't have a choice!
仕方ないでしょ
Can you imagine how much I had to persuade my mom?
どれだけお母さんの説得に時間がかかったか…
Money!
金
What are you doing?!
何のつもりだ
At least... At least a thousand!
せめて せめて1,000円だけでも
Geez...
Take them.
持っていきな
Doc, you miser!
ドクの業突張り
This is how pros roll.
これがプロの仕事だ
I got the gyro and other necessary parts too.
それから一応 ジャイロと必要そうなパーツも用意してある
If you really want to win, you'll need at least these.
本気で勝ちてえんなら これくらいやらなきゃ駄目って話だ
Oh!
15 thousand altogether.
締めて1万5,000だ
Oh please! I'll do whatever it takes, except for money!
もう お金以外なら何でもするから
でも 痛いのとエッチィなのは駄目
But nothing painful or perverted.
You're barely past bedwetter age. Who'd want that from you?!
誰がてめえみたいなしょんべん臭えがきに んなこと要求する
You're mean! I'll sue you!
ひどい 訴えたい
We'll pay with the money we win from the Robo-One.
ROBO-ONEの優勝賞金で払うよ
Will that do for those parts?
そのパーツ代
だったら いいだろ
Kai... Just now that was really cool.
カイ 今の最高にクールだった
That'll do, won't it?
そうだよ それならいいでしょ
You're underestimating the adults.
お前ら 大人なめてんだろ
But that's the rocker spirit.
だが
ロックだな
それからのアキちゃんは夢中だった
After that, Aki became obsessed.
She rebuilt the Tanegashimachine-3,
時に自分で調べ 時にドクに協力を仰ぎ
sometimes looking stuff up by herself and sometimes asking Doc for help,
even sacrificing sleep for it.
寝る間を惜しんで タネガシマシン3を組み立てていった
She was so obsessed it made me worry.
俺が不安になってしまうほどに
Morning...
おはよう
You're late.
遅い
This is what you get for calling me out on a Sunday.
日曜に呼び出されてこの時間で来たんだよ
It's still early for me.
むしろ 早い方
それが完成品?
You finished it?
Look! Tanegashimachine-3 has been reborn!
見よ これがタネガシマシン3の生まれ変わった姿
名付けて タネガシマシン3改
I name it the Tanegashimachine-3S!
You had enough screws?
ねじ ちゃんと足りた?
That's the first thing you've gotta say?
第一声がそれ?
It's fine. Doc helped with the stuff we lacked.
大丈夫 足りないのはドクに何とかしてもらったし
So you were missing parts?
やっぱり足りなかったんだ
The point is that it's done now.
とにかく完成したから いいの
ではこれより 起動テストを開始する
Now I shall commence the activation test!
Whoa...
すごい
Once you turn it on, the servos reset to the default position.
スイッチを入れると
サーボモーターが決められたホームポジションに戻るの
And now I'll show off my skills.
で ここからが腕の見せどころ
Whoops, my bad.
間違えた
What's wrong?
どうしたの
Whoa, so many switches!
何? そのスイッチの数
I didn't know it was this complicated.
こんなに複雑だったんだ
Can you really do it?
できるの
It was complicated back then too, so no one could use it.
当時も複雑過ぎて 誰もできなかった
でも お姉ちゃんだけは完璧に使いこなしていて
But my sister mastered it perfectly, and defeated the opponents one after another.
次々敵を倒していったんだ
And you want to master it in a week?
それをアキちゃんは あと1週間で使いこなそうっていうの
Yeah...
見えるぞ 私にも敵が見える
I can see it! I can see the enemy too!
No, you can't.
無理だよ
もう 諦める暇があったらとにかく練習するの
If I have time to give up, I have time to practice!
あっ 倒れた
It fell down.
Perfect.
よし ちょうどいい 見ててよ
Look now!
What do you think?
どう
必殺 タネガシアクセルインパクト
Finishing move! Tanegashi Accel Impact!
パクリじゃん
You stole that idea.
What about brakes?
ブレーキは?
ない
There aren't any.
カイ 走って
Run, Kai!
Eh?!
This won't do...
駄目か
Can we go home yet?
そろそろお開きにしたら?
Um...
Really you should be the operator.
やっぱりカイがオペレーターやった方がいいよ
It'd be the same regardless. It's complicated.
誰がやっても一緒だよ そんな難しいの
But your fingers move just like my sister's...
でもその指の動き お姉ちゃんにも負けてないよ
それは 『キルバラ』だか…
Yeah, fitting for Kill Ballad.
アキちゃん
Aki...
Sorry.
ごめん
How are you feeling?
体調は?
Fine...
平気
You're not fine, are you?
平気じゃないよね
ごめん 来るかも
I can feel it coming...
What now? Go somewhere?
どうする? 移動する?
No, it'll be fine here.
ううん ここでいい
The Elephant Mouse syndrome.
エレファントマウス症候群
Basically, it's fast forward.
要は 早回しだ
When she has a spasm,
発作が起きると アキちゃんは5分間に起きたことを1秒で体感する
Aki processes five minutes as one second.
It all started nine years ago with that accident...
全ては 9年前のあの事故から
Kai...
カイ カイ
カイ
Kai...
Is it over?
終わった?
Yeah.
I'll call your mom.
おばさんに連絡しとくよ
It only happens when you're tired,
疲れると すぐ出るんだから
so learn from this and don't overexert yourself.
これに懲りて 無茶はしないこと
Okay?
分かった?
Mhm...
You still answer like that?
この期に及んで まだその返事?
Then...
じゃあさ カイ オペレーターやってくれないかな
Will you be the operator?
Without a Kill Ballad battle.
『キルバラ』勝負なしで
ずるいな
That's not fair.
Okay.
分かった
Really?
本当?
ただし プロポを『キルバラ』みたいな操縦方法にしてくれたらね
But only if you make the controls like Kill Ballad.
With so little time left? Is that possible?
今から?
できるかな
It is. We have a trump card.
できるよ
実は当てがある
Sorry for the sudden msg...
It's a bit tough to say, but you see...
I suspect you of cheating, UMISHO.
Your reactions are abnormally fast. Grandma always—
lol, I mean, we've received a message saying so.
If you've anything to say about that, tell us.
フラウ コウジロー?
FRAUKOUJIRO?
Sorry for the sudden msg...
It's a bit tough to say, but you see...
I suspect you of cheating, UMISHO.
Your reactions are abnormally fast. Grandma always—
lol, I mean, we've received a message saying so.
If you've anything to say about that, tell us.
Sorry for the sudden msg...
It's a bit tough to say, but you see...
I suspect you of cheating, UMISHO.
Your reactions are abnormally fast. Grandma always—
lol, I mean, we've received a message saying so.
If you've anything to say about that, tell us.
Sorry for the sudden msg...
It's a bit tough to say, but you see...
I suspect you of cheating, UMISHO.
Your reactions are abnormally fast. Grandma always—
lol, I mean, we've received a message saying so.
If you've anything to say about that, tell us.
Sorry for the sudden msg...
It's a bit tough to say, but you see...
I suspect you of cheating, UMISHO.
Your reactions are abnormally fast. Grandma always—
lol, I mean, we've received a message saying so.
If you've anything to say about that, tell us.
I told you, he created Kill Ballad.
Sorry for the sudden msg...
It's a bit tough to say, but you see...
I suspect you of cheating, UMISHO.
Your reactions are abnormally fast. Grandma always—
lol, I mean, we've received a message saying so.
If you've anything to say about that, tell us.
言ったろ 『キルバラ』の制作者
Sorry for the sudden msg...
It's a bit tough to say, but you see...
I suspect you of cheating, UMISHO.
Your reactions are abnormally fast. Grandma always—
lol, I mean, we've received a message saying so.
If you've anything to say about that, tell us.
Sorry for the sudden msg...
It's a bit tough to say, but you see...
I suspect you of cheating, UMISHO.
Your reactions are abnormally fast. Grandma always—
lol, I mean, we've received a message saying so.
If you've anything to say about that, tell us.
Sorry for the sudden msg...
It's a bit tough to say, but you see...
I suspect you of cheating, UMISHO.
Your reactions are abnormally fast. Grandma always—
lol, I mean, we've received a message saying so.
If you've anything to say about that, tell us.
Sorry for the sudden msg...
It's a bit tough to say, but you see...
I suspect you of cheating, UMISHO.
Your reactions are abnormally fast. Grandma always—
lol, I mean, we've received a message saying so.
If you've anything to say about that, tell us.
Sorry for the sudden msg...
It's a bit tough to say, but you see...
I suspect you of cheating, UMISHO.
Your reactions are abnormally fast. Grandma always—
lol, I mean, we've received a message saying so.
If you've anything to say about that, tell us.
Sorry for the sudden msg...
It's a bit tough to say, but you see...
I suspect you of cheating, UMISHO.
Your reactions are abnormally fast. Grandma always—
lol, I mean, we've received a message saying so.
If you've anything to say about that, tell us.
Sorry for the sudden msg...
It's a bit tough to say, but you see...
I suspect you of cheating, UMISHO.
Your reactions are abnormally fast. Grandma always—
lol, I mean, we've received a message saying so.
If you've anything to say about that, tell us.
Sorry for the sudden msg...
It's a bit tough to say, but you see...
I suspect you of cheating, UMISHO.
Your reactions are abnormally fast. Grandma always—
lol, I mean, we've received a message saying so.
If you've anything to say about that, tell us.
Sorry for the sudden msg...
It's a bit tough to say, but you see...
I suspect you of cheating, UMISHO.
Your reactions are abnormally fast. Grandma always—
lol, I mean, we've received a message saying so.
If you've anything to say about that, tell us.
Sorry for the sudden msg...
It's a bit tough to say, but you see...
I suspect you of cheating, UMISHO.
Your reactions are abnormally fast. Grandma always—
lol, I mean, we've received a message saying so.
If you've anything to say about that, tell us.
Sorry for the sudden msg...
It's a bit tough to say, but you see...
I suspect you of cheating, UMISHO.
Your reactions are abnormally fast. Grandma always—
lol, I mean, we've received a message saying so.
If you've anything to say about that, tell us.
Sorry for the sudden msg...
It's a bit tough to say, but you see...
I suspect you of cheating, UMISHO.
Your reactions are abnormally fast. Grandma always—
lol, I mean, we've received a message saying so.
If you've anything to say about that, tell us.
Sorry for the sudden msg...
It's a bit tough to say, but you see...
I suspect you of cheating, UMISHO.
Your reactions are abnormally fast. Grandma always—
lol, I mean, we've received a message saying so.
If you've anything to say about that, tell us.
Sorry for the sudden msg...
It's a bit tough to say, but you see...
I suspect you of cheating, UMISHO.
Your reactions are abnormally fast. Grandma always—
lol, I mean, we've received a message saying so.
If you've anything to say about that, tell us.
Sorry for the sudden msg...
It's a bit tough to say, but you see...
I suspect you of cheating, UMISHO.
Your reactions are abnormally fast. Grandma always—
lol, I mean, we've received a message saying so.
If you've anything to say about that, tell us.
Sorry for the sudden msg...
It's a bit tough to say, but you see...
I suspect you of cheating, UMISHO.
Your reactions are abnormally fast. Grandma always—
lol, I mean, we've received a message saying so.
If you've anything to say about that, tell us.
Sorry for the sudden msg...
It's a bit tough to say, but you see...
I suspect you of cheating, UMISHO.
Your reactions are abnormally fast. Grandma always—
lol, I mean, we've received a message saying so.
If you've anything to say about that, tell us.
Sorry for the sudden msg...
It's a bit tough to say, but you see...
I suspect you of cheating, UMISHO.
Your reactions are abnormally fast. Grandma always—
lol, I mean, we've received a message saying so.
If you've anything to say about that, tell us.
Sorry for the sudden msg...
It's a bit tough to say, but you see...
I suspect you of cheating, UMISHO.
Your reactions are abnormally fast. Grandma always—
lol, I mean, we've received a message saying so.
If you've anything to say about that, tell us.
Sorry for the sudden msg...
It's a bit tough to say, but you see...
I suspect you of cheating, UMISHO.
Your reactions are abnormally fast. Grandma always—
lol, I mean, we've received a message saying so.
If you've anything to say about that, tell us.
Sorry for the sudden msg...
It's a bit tough to say, but you see...
I suspect you of cheating, UMISHO.
Your reactions are abnormally fast. Grandma always—
lol, I mean, we've received a message saying so.
If you've anything to say about that, tell us.
Sorry for the sudden msg...
It's a bit tough to say, but you see...
I suspect you of cheating, UMISHO.
Your reactions are abnormally fast. Grandma always—
lol, I mean, we've received a message saying so.
If you've anything to say about that, tell us.
Sorry for the sudden msg...
It's a bit tough to say, but you see...
I suspect you of cheating, UMISHO.
Your reactions are abnormally fast. Grandma always—
lol, I mean, we've received a message saying so.
If you've anything to say about that, tell us.
Sorry for the sudden msg...
It's a bit tough to say, but you see...
I suspect you of cheating, UMISHO.
Your reactions are abnormally fast. Grandma always—
lol, I mean, we've received a message saying so.
If you've anything to say about that, tell us.
Sorry for the sudden msg...
It's a bit tough to say, but you see...
I suspect you of cheating, UMISHO.
Your reactions are abnormally fast. Grandma always—
lol, I mean, we've received a message saying so.
If you've anything to say about that, tell us.
Sorry for the sudden msg...
It's a bit tough to say, but you see...
I suspect you of cheating, UMISHO.
Your reactions are abnormally fast. Grandma always—
lol, I mean, we've received a message saying so.
If you've anything to say about that, tell us.
Sorry for the sudden msg...
It's a bit tough to say, but you see...
I suspect you of cheating, UMISHO.
Your reactions are abnormally fast. Grandma always—
lol, I mean, we've received a message saying so.
If you've anything to say about that, tell us.
Sorry for the sudden msg...
It's a bit tough to say, but you see...
I suspect you of cheating, UMISHO.
Your reactions are abnormally fast. Grandma always—
lol, I mean, we've received a message saying so.
If you've anything to say about that, tell us.
Sorry for the sudden msg...
It's a bit tough to say, but you see...
I suspect you of cheating, UMISHO.
Your reactions are abnormally fast. Grandma always—
lol, I mean, we've received a message saying so.
If you've anything to say about that, tell us.
Sorry for the sudden msg...
It's a bit tough to say, but you see...
I suspect you of cheating, UMISHO.
Your reactions are abnormally fast. Grandma always—
lol, I mean, we've received a message saying so.
If you've anything to say about that, tell us.
Sorry for the sudden msg...
It's a bit tough to say, but you see...
I suspect you of cheating, UMISHO.
Your reactions are abnormally fast. Grandma always—
lol, I mean, we've received a message saying so.
If you've anything to say about that, tell us.
Sorry for the sudden msg...
It's a bit tough to say, but you see...
I suspect you of cheating, UMISHO.
Your reactions are abnormally fast. Grandma always—
lol, I mean, we've received a message saying so.
If you've anything to say about that, tell us.
Sorry for the sudden msg...
It's a bit tough to say, but you see...
I suspect you of cheating, UMISHO.
Your reactions are abnormally fast. Grandma always—
lol, I mean, we've received a message saying so.
If you've anything to say about that, tell us.
Sorry for the sudden msg...
It's a bit tough to say, but you see...
I suspect you of cheating, UMISHO.
Your reactions are abnormally fast. Grandma always—
lol, I mean, we've received a message saying so.
If you've anything to say about that, tell us.
Sorry for the sudden msg...
It's a bit tough to say, but you see...
I suspect you of cheating, UMISHO.
Your reactions are abnormally fast. Grandma always—
lol, I mean, we've received a message saying so.
If you've anything to say about that, tell us.
Sorry for the sudden msg...
It's a bit tough to say, but you see...
I suspect you of cheating, UMISHO.
Your reactions are abnormally fast. Grandma always—
lol, I mean, we've received a message saying so.
If you've anything to say about that, tell us.
Sorry for the sudden msg...
It's a bit tough to say, but you see...
I suspect you of cheating, UMISHO.
Your reactions are abnormally fast. Grandma always—
lol, I mean, we've received a message saying so.
If you've anything to say about that, tell us.
Sorry for the sudden msg...
It's a bit tough to say, but you see...
I suspect you of cheating, UMISHO.
Your reactions are abnormally fast. Grandma always—
lol, I mean, we've received a message saying so.
If you've anything to say about that, tell us.
Sorry for the sudden msg...
It's a bit tough to say, but you see...
I suspect you of cheating, UMISHO.
Your reactions are abnormally fast. Grandma always—
lol, I mean, we've received a message saying so.
If you've anything to say about that, tell us.
Sorry for the sudden msg...
It's a bit tough to say, but you see...
I suspect you of cheating, UMISHO.
Your reactions are abnormally fast. Grandma always—
lol, I mean, we've received a message saying so.
If you've anything to say about that, tell us.
Sorry for the sudden msg...
It's a bit tough to say, but you see...
I suspect you of cheating, UMISHO.
Your reactions are abnormally fast. Grandma always—
lol, I mean, we've received a message saying so.
If you've anything to say about that, tell us.
Sorry for the sudden msg...
It's a bit tough to say, but you see...
I suspect you of cheating, UMISHO.
Your reactions are abnormally fast. Grandma always—
lol, I mean, we've received a message saying so.
If you've anything to say about that, tell us.
Sorry for the sudden msg...
It's a bit tough to say, but you see...
I suspect you of cheating, UMISHO.
Your reactions are abnormally fast. Grandma always—
lol, I mean, we've received a message saying so.
If you've anything to say about that, tell us.
Sorry for the sudden msg...
It's a bit tough to say, but you see...
I suspect you of cheating, UMISHO.
Your reactions are abnormally fast. Grandma always—
lol, I mean, we've received a message saying so.
If you've anything to say about that, tell us.
Sorry for the sudden msg...
It's a bit tough to say, but you see...
I suspect you of cheating, UMISHO.
Your reactions are abnormally fast. Grandma always—
lol, I mean, we've received a message saying so.
If you've anything to say about that, tell us.
Sorry for the sudden msg...
It's a bit tough to say, but you see...
I suspect you of cheating, UMISHO.
Your reactions are abnormally fast. Grandma always—
lol, I mean, we've received a message saying so.
If you've anything to say about that, tell us.
Sorry for the sudden msg...
It's a bit tough to say, but you see...
I suspect you of cheating, UMISHO.
Your reactions are abnormally fast. Grandma always—
lol, I mean, we've received a message saying so.
If you've anything to say about that, tell us.
Sorry for the sudden msg...
It's a bit tough to say, but you see...
I suspect you of cheating, UMISHO.
Your reactions are abnormally fast. Grandma always—
lol, I mean, we've received a message saying so.
If you've anything to say about that, tell us.
Sorry for the sudden msg...
It's a bit tough to say, but you see...
I suspect you of cheating, UMISHO.
Your reactions are abnormally fast. Grandma always—
lol, I mean, we've received a message saying so.
If you've anything to say about that, tell us.
Sorry for the sudden msg...
It's a bit tough to say, but you see...
I suspect you of cheating, UMISHO.
Your reactions are abnormally fast. Grandma always—
lol, I mean, we've received a message saying so.
If you've anything to say about that, tell us.
Sorry for the sudden msg...
It's a bit tough to say, but you see...
I suspect you of cheating, UMISHO.
Your reactions are abnormally fast. Grandma always—
lol, I mean, we've received a message saying so.
If you've anything to say about that, tell us.
Sorry for the sudden msg...
It's a bit tough to say, but you see...
I suspect you of cheating, UMISHO.
Your reactions are abnormally fast. Grandma always—
lol, I mean, we've received a message saying so.
If you've anything to say about that, tell us.
Sorry for the sudden msg...
It's a bit tough to say, but you see...
I suspect you of cheating, UMISHO.
Your reactions are abnormally fast. Grandma always—
lol, I mean, we've received a message saying so.
If you've anything to say about that, tell us.
Sorry for the sudden msg...
It's a bit tough to say, but you see...
I suspect you of cheating, UMISHO.
Your reactions are abnormally fast. Grandma always—
lol, I mean, we've received a message saying so.
If you've anything to say about that, tell us.
Sorry for the sudden msg...
It's a bit tough to say, but you see...
I suspect you of cheating, UMISHO.
Your reactions are abnormally fast. Grandma always—
lol, I mean, we've received a message saying so.
If you've anything to say about that, tell us.
Sorry for the sudden msg...
It's a bit tough to say, but you see...
I suspect you of cheating, UMISHO.
Your reactions are abnormally fast. Grandma always—
lol, I mean, we've received a message saying so.
If you've anything to say about that, tell us.
Sorry for the sudden msg...
It's a bit tough to say, but you see...
I suspect you of cheating, UMISHO.
Your reactions are abnormally fast. Grandma always—
lol, I mean, we've received a message saying so.
If you've anything to say about that, tell us.
Sorry for the sudden msg...
It's a bit tough to say, but you see...
I suspect you of cheating, UMISHO.
Your reactions are abnormally fast. Grandma always—
lol, I mean, we've received a message saying so.
If you've anything to say about that, tell us.
Sorry for the sudden msg...
It's a bit tough to say, but you see...
I suspect you of cheating, UMISHO.
Your reactions are abnormally fast. Grandma always—
lol, I mean, we've received a message saying so.
If you've anything to say about that, tell us.
He has all the code of Kill Ballad.
『キルバラ』の全てのプログラムを持ってる人
Don't you think it's worth asking?
頼んでみる価値はあると思わない?
I see!
そっか
Now I'm on fire! I'm on fire!
たぎってきた たぎってきた
Come on, you're exhausted, so stay still.
こら 疲れてんだから おとなしくして
No! We don't have time!
駄目 もう時間がないんだから
Get in touch with him right away! Right away!
すぐ連絡取って すぐ
Okay, okay...
はいはい
Senomiya Akiho
Incoming call
Accept
Away
Senomiya Akiho
Incoming call
Accept
Senomiya Akiho
Incoming call
Accept
Away
Senomiya Akiho
Incoming call
Accept
Away
Senomiya Akiho
Incoming call
Accept
Away
Senomiya Akiho
Incoming call
Accept
Away
幼い思い出　眩しい波光に
The blinding light of childhood memories
夢に見た景色は
Turns the scenery of my dream
Into monochrome as it lies forgotten
置き忘れたまま
モノクロになって
瞳から消える
And vanishes from my eyes
だけどいつでも君は
But you've always been
Looking straight at the future
まっすぐ明日を見つめた
どれくらいの涙と引き換えに
And you paid the price in tears
So we turn our hesitation
だから僕らの迷いも
強さに変えてくれる
Into strength by the power
Of our connected hearts
繋がった心が解き放つ
Feel it! These overflowing emotions
不意に溢れ出す思い
For that someone in the sunset
同じに誰かのために
I'll use the little courage I have
この小さな勇気で
風が吹き荒れても
And overcome the rage of the wind
Because I want to protect you
君を守りたくて
Tune in next week too!
Yo
!!